<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://greensupply.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://greensupply.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://greensupply.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Greensupply.com - News</title>
  <updated>2020-08-19T14:50:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Greensupply.com</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://greensupply.com/blogs/news/is-green-supply-legit</id>
    <published>2020-08-19T14:50:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-08-19T14:54:05-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://greensupply.com/blogs/news/is-green-supply-legit"/>
    <title>Is Green Supply Legit?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Service Account</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>2020 has been a year to remember. The global pandemic, has had a huge impact on the </span><span>world</span><span> economy, leading to multiple businesses and organization having to make significant cuts or close their doors altogether. However, some businesses were able to alter their focus and become an “essential” business during the 2020 pandemic. According to Herd (2020), a writer for Maxim, Green Supply was able to accomplish and strive despite the horrid downfall of the United States and global economy. </span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://greensupply.com/blogs/news/is-green-supply-legit">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>2020 has been a year to remember. The global pandemic, has had a huge impact on the world economy, leading to multiple businesses and organization having to make significant cuts or close their doors altogether. However, some businesses were able to alter their focus and become an “essential” business during the 2020 pandemic. According to Herd (2020), a writer for Maxim, Green Supply was able to accomplish and strive despite the horrid downfall of the United States and global economy. </p>
<p><br> One may ask, “Is Green Supply Legit?” Chad Horstman from Scottsdale, Arizona, co-founder of Yandy.com, a woman’s sexy costume and lingerie company was the main founder of Green Supply. He began Green Supply with a dedication, love, and passion for health and wellness, crafting a business that supports the wellbeing of others. Horstman originally planned to launch a CBD oil line and additional wellness products. However, like many, Horstman suppliers were negatively impacted due to the global pandemic virus. Utilizing the networking of his successful partner, an international luxury jeweler designer, Josh Helmich, the duo was able to quickly shift their focus to essential products. <br><br>The team, keeping wellness in mind not only developed a trusted <a href="https://greensupply.com/collections/hand-sanitizer">hand sanitizer </a>equipped with the necessary ingredients to destroy deadly viruses and bacteria, but eliminated the harmful substance many sanitizers carry. In addition, they were able to provide individuals with <a href="https://greensupply.com/products/kn95-mask-for-sale">KN95 masks</a>, <a href="https://greensupply.com/collections/face-masks/cloth">cloth face masks</a>, and <a href="https://greensupply.com/products/disposable-blue-face-masks-50-pack">blue disposable masks</a> at reasonable prices. Since the beginning of the pandemic the Green Supply team has continued to expand and carry additional essential supplies including goggles, face shields, a variety of <a href="https://greensupply.com/collections/gloves">gloves</a>, <a href="https://greensupply.com/collections/health-and-wellness/uv">UV light Sanitizer boxes</a>, <a href="https://greensupply.com/products/infrared-forehead-thermometer">thermometers</a>, and a selection of sanitizers. Green Supply has over customer reviews stating consumer satisfaction due to the trusted and responsive costumer services team, the highly skilled sales department, outstanding leadership, and excellent products. Furthermore, Green Supply has been featured on Yahoo Finance, International Business Times, and Maxim among others as a leader in the field.<br> <br>Green Supply continues to provide excellent service to all consumers. The wellness company offers wholesale options, individual small purchases, and frequent giveaways for first responders. Green Supply’s goal is to provide the consumer with affordable products and access to trusted wellness essentials during this difficult time. In addition, Green Supply continues to work on the launch of their CBD oil and organic essential oil, which will be coming soon. Green Supply is here to support the community and be your top choice for essential health and wellness products.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://greensupply.com/blogs/news/how-to-wear-a-kn95-mask</id>
    <published>2020-05-05T20:05:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-06T10:04:51-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://greensupply.com/blogs/news/how-to-wear-a-kn95-mask"/>
    <title>How to Wear a KN95 Mask</title>
    <author>
      <name>Service Account</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Learn the 5 steps to properly wear a KN95 face mask with help from the Green Supply blog.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://greensupply.com/blogs/news/how-to-wear-a-kn95-mask">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uL8ndBer6bk" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></span></p>
<p>As many countries including the United States have started to ease COVID-19 restrictions the World Health Organization and the Center for Disease Control and Prevention are directing the public to wear masks when in public space. Wearing a mask helps to prevent the transmission among individuals who may be a carrier or ill with COIVD-19. At Green Supply we want to ensure you take the correct steps when wearing your mask. Listed below are the steps you can take to ensure you are properly wearing your mask. </p>
<br>
<p><b>How to wear a mask:</b></p>
<br>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 1) Perform hand hygiene before putting on your mask. </span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 2) Hold the KN95 in your palm with the nosepiece at the fingertips and allow for the head straps to hang freely below your hand. </span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 3) While holding the KN95 in place, pull the left strap over your ear and do the same with the right strap</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 4) Using both hands, mold the nosepiece to the shape of your nose by pushing downward and outward. While moving your fingertips down both sides of the nosepiece. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You are officially wearing your KN95. </span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Step 5) Perform hand hygiene after putting on mask. </span></p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
